http://www.midwestsupplies.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Notice
Midwest Supplies knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting midwestsupplies.com or interacting with Midwest Supplies in any other way, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy notice.
What Personal Information About Customers Does Midwest Supplies Gather?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your experience. Here are the types of information we gather.
Information You Give Us. We receive and store any information you enter on our web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.
You provide most such information when you search, buy, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product or place an order through Midwest Supplies; provide information in your account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us); communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; use our services such as Brewing TV; compile wish lists or other gift registries; participate in discussion boards or other community features; provide and rate reviews and specify a reminder. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers; credit card information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including addresses and phone number; people (with addresses and phone numbers); e-mail addresses of your friends and other people; content of reviews and e-mails to us; and personal description and photograph in your account or profile.
Automatic Information. We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many web sites, we use cookies and we obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses midwestsupplies.com or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Midwest Supplies on other web sites.
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create features like top sellers; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and the phone number you used to call our 800 number. We may also use browser data such as cookies, or similar data on certain parts of our Web site for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. We may also collect technical information to help us identify your device for fraud prevention and diagnostic purposes.
E-mail Communications. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please contact us to adjust your customer communication preferences.
This website uses social media plugins. Even without being a user of these social media sites, your IP-address is transmitted to the servers of the social media company.
Information from Other Sources. We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.
Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.
How does Midwest Supplies Share the Information It Receives?
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we do not sell it to others. We share customer information only as described below and with parent companies that control us and subsidiaries we control that either are subject to this privacy notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this privacy notice.
Third-Party Service Providers. We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail (catalogs, postcards, gift cards, etc) and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
Business Transfers. As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, business units or the entire business. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing privacy notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Midwest Supplies or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. Please be aware that we may transfer your personal information to the [European Union] or to another country where privacy standards may not be equivalent to those in your country.
Protection of Midwest Supplies and Others. We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Midwest Supplies, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
With Your Consent. Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
What Choices Do I Have?
As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such features as your account, wish lists and customer reviews.
You can add or update certain information on pages such as your account. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please contact us to adjust your communication preferences though if you do not want to receive Conditions of Use and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of this website, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.
The help feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Midwest Supplies's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any Midwest Supplies products and services that require you to sign in.
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to visit midwestsupplies.com or interact with Midwest Supplies in any other way, your visit and interaction and any dispute over privacy is subject to this notice and our conditions of use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the State of Minnesota. If you have any concern about privacy at Midwest Supplies, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly, and our privacy notice and the conditions of use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but you should check our web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
DIGITAL MILLENNIUM COPYRIGHT ACTMidwest Supplies is committed to respecting and protecting the legal rights of copyright owners. As such, Midwest Supplies adheres to the following notice and take down policy, in full compliance with Section 512(c)(3) of the DMCA (17 U.S.C. § 512 et seq.). If you believe any of the Content infringes upon your intellectual property rights, please submit a notification alleging such infringement (hereafter a “DMCA Takedown Notice”). To be valid, a DMCA Takedown Notice must (i) be provided to Midwest Supplies’s designated agent, (“Copyright Agent”), as set forth below, and (ii) include the following:
A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;
Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works;
Identification of the material claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access disabled and information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to locate the material;
Information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to contact you, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic mail;
A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and
A statement that, under penalty of perjury, the information in the notification is accurate and you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
Midwest Supplies’s Copyright Agent to receive DMCA Takedown Notices is: email: service@midwestsupplies.com. For clarity, only DMCA Takedown Notices should go to the Copyright Agent; any other feedback, comments, online purchases or other communications should be directed to the applicable customer service links posted on the Website. You acknowledge that in order for Midwest Supplies to be authorized to takedown any Content, your DMCA Takedown Notice must comply with all of the requirements of this Section.
